audiotrimmer.com 2018-10-31

# Privacy Policy | Audio Trimmer

At audiotrimmer.com we consider the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information is collected and recorded by audiotrimmer.com and how we use it.

## Uploaded Content

Audio Trimmer helps its users trim their audio files online. The uploaded audio content is stored in temporary folders on our servers to perform these operations. Files uploaded to Audio Trimmer are automatically deleted from our servers at regular intervals. We don't store or save your content permanently and don't make your content publicly available in any form.

## Log Files

Like many other Web sites, audiotrimmer.com makes use of log files. These files merely include raw visitor traffic to the site. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

## Cookies and Web Beacons

Audio Trimmer doesn't use cookies to collect personal information although our third party partners, such as Google Adsense and Google Analytics, might use cookies to record general data about your visit, such as your IP address, user agent, country, etc. Our third party partners:

### DoubleClick DART Cookie

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on audiotrimmer.com.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our site's visitors based upon their visit to audiotrimmer.com and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL \- <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

### Google Analytics

Audio Trimmer uses Google Analytics as a third party service to record and analyse the traffic to audiotrimmer.com. Google Analytics basically records data about your visit to Audio Trimmer, such as, your IP address, user agent, location, duration of your visit, pages you browsed etc. These information doesn't include personally identifying data.

For more info about the cookies Google use, please visit <http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/>

## Consent

By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms. We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time as we update the functionality and services provided on Audio Trimmer. It is your responsibility to check this page regularly to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
